Guide to the New York Times Company records. Arthur Hays Sulzberger papers
New York Public Library
- Series I. People, 1873, 1884-1968, 1972, 1975, n.d; 86.25 boxes, 1 volume
  - Hechinger, Fred M., 1959-1961 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Heckman, Harrison J., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Heckscher, August
  - Hefter, Robert
  - Hegi, Edward A., 1954-1967 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Heidinger, Clifford F., 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Heifetz, Florence Vidor, 1954-1961 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Heifetz, Jascha, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Heiner, Marie Hays, 1950-1954 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Heiskell, Andrew, 1960-1968 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Heiskell, Marian Sulzberger Dryfoos, 1965-1968 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Hellman, Geoffrey T., 1942 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Hellman, George S., 1953, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Helm, Harold H., 1957-1966 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Heming, Lucile, 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Henderson, Leon, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Henderson, Loy
  - Hendricks, Rosalie, 1959, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Henriques, Basil L. Q., 1942-1944 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Hense, Florence, 1936-1946 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Herman, Tessie Dryfoos, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Hermann, Rudolf, 1948-1954 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Herrick, Elinore M., 1935-1964 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Hershey, Lewis B.
  - Herter, Christian A., 1956-1961 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Herts, Henry Beaumont
  - Herzog, Jean, 1949-1951 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Herzog, Leo Sulzberger, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Herzog, Julie d' Estournelles
  - Herzog, Rose A., 1949 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Hesmondhalgh, W. B. and Iris Hesmondhalgh, 1957, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Hess, Sara Straus, 1951-1960 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Hess, Thomas, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Heusinger, Ruth, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Heyman, David M., 1956-1968 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Heymann, Curt L., 1927, 1934, 1944-1948 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    Heyman was a German journalist who worked for The New York Times as a reporter from 1934 to 1948, and served with the U.S. Office of War Information in 1944-1945, while on leave from the Times.Heyman was a German journalist who worked for The New York Times as a reporter from 1934 to 1948, and served with the U.S. Office of War Information in 1944-1945, while on leave from the Times.
  - Heymanson, Randal
  - Higgins, Charters K., 1951-1960 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Higley, Elizabeth Parrott, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Hill, George W., Jr. and Gretchen Hill, 1956-1966 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Hill, Gladwin, 1946-1955 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Hill, N. C., 1935-1964 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Hilliard, Raymond M., 1948-1958 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Hills, Lee, 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Himmell, Sam S., 1957 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Hincks, Carroll C.
  - Hinkel, John V., 1965 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Hinton, Harold B., 1933-1954 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Hirschmann, Ira A., 1935-1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Hirshfeld, Al
  - Hiss, Alger
  - Hitler, Adolf
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1956-1964 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Hochschild, Harold K., 1936-1968 (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
  - Hochschild, Walter, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Hoffman, Calvin, 1951, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Hoffman, Isidor B.
  - Hoffman, Malvina, 1951-1964 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Hoffman, Michael L., 1945-1956 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Hoffmann, Paul G., 1948-1950, 1961-1965 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Hogan, Frank S., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Hogan, John V. L., 1947, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Holden, Oliver
  - Hollenbeck, Don, 1947-1948, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Hollister, Paul, 1957-1962 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Holloway, Hubert, 1953, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Holmberg, William A.
  - Holt, Hamilton
  - Homer, Sidney, 1959, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Homolka, Oscar, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Hood, Ronald C.
  - Hoover, J. Edgar
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1932, 1940-1951, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Includes Arthur Krock's report on his conversation with Hoover, April 20, 1932.
  - Hopkins, Ernest Martin
  - Hopper, Bruce C., 1947-1964 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Hopper, Hedda, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Horan, Anne
  - Horkheimer, Max, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Horne, George, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Horne, Joshua L., 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Hotchkis, Preston, 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Hotopp, Carl F., 1954-1956, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Houghton, Amory, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Houghton, Arthur A., Jr., 1958-1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Hoving, Walter, 1943, 1955-1961, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Howard, Jack R., 1962-1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Howard, Roy W., 1946-1964 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Howe, Dorothy Cheesman and Raymond R. Howe, Jr., 1954, 1959, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Howkins, Elizabeth Penrose, 1956-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Hoxie, R. Gordon, 1952-1953, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Hoyes, Frank B.
  - Hoyt, E. Palmer and Edwin P. Hoyt, 1946-1967 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Hu, Shih, 1942, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Huger, Louise P., 1957-1958, 1966-1968 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Hughes, Richard J., 1961-1967 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Hulen, Bertram D.
  - Hull, Cordell, 1934, 1942-1948 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Hulsart, C. Raymond, 1953-1967 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Humphrey, George M., 1957, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Humphrey, Howard R., 1942, 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1956-1967 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Hunt, Lawrence, 1941, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Hunt, Virginia L., 1957-1968 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Hunter, Maxwell W., II
  - Hurd, Charles, 1941-1949, 1954, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Hurley, Patrick J., 1943 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Hurst, Fannie, 1944, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Huston, Luther A., 1938-1941, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Hutchins, Robert Maynard
  - Hutchinson, George R., 1950-1952 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Hutton, Edward F., 1946-1949 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Hyde, Donald R., 1942 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Iacovone, Giacomo and Therese Raick Iacovone
  - Ickes, Harold L., 1935-1946 (Box 34, Folder 28-30)
  - Igleheart, Austin S., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Illava, Karl, 1927, 1946-1948 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Immanuel, Max, 1939-1950 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Ingalls, Roscoe C., 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph M.
  - Inman, Philip
  - Isaac, Robert and Lucille Isaac, 1953-1967 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Isaacs, Stanley M. and Edith Isaacs, 1957, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Ives, Elizabeth Stevenson, 1958, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Jack, Hulan E., 1954-1957 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, C. D., 1948-1953, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Robert H., 1940 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, William H., 1953 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Jacobs, Albert C., 1951-1962 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Jacobs, Joseph E., 1949 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Jaffe, Herman, 1942-1959 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - James, Edwin L. and Simone James
    James was a distinguished war correspondent and foreign correspondent of the NYT and was its managing editor from 1932 to his death in 1951.
    - General, 1930-1958 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      This folder contains his correspondence with AHS about personal and miscellaneous business matters and correspondence with his widow, mostly about financial arrangements.
    - Condolence Messages, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      The next folder contains condolence messages addressed to AHS, arranged alphebetically.
  - James, Michael, 1949-1965 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - James, Reese D.
  - Jansen, William, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Jaretzki, Alfred, Jr., 1938-1942, 1960-1968 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Jarman, W. Maxey, 1956, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1954-1968 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Jay, John
  - Jay, Nelson Dean, 1960, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Jebb, Gladwyn
  - Jefferson, Thomas
  - Jenkins, Dorothy H.
  - Jenks, Edward N., 1946, 1953, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Jennings, Naomi, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Jerome, Leonard W.
  - Jewell, Alden
  - Jirak, Josephine, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Joham, Josef
  - John, Emil Paul, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1954-1959 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Gerald W., 1955-1956 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Johnson, John Henry, 1955-1956 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Joseph E., 1951, 1956-1957 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Johnson, Louis A., 1949, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1955-1964 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Johnson, Martin
  - Johnson, Osa Helen Leighty
  - Johnson, T. Walter
  - Johnson, U. Alexis, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    Includes James Reston's report on his confidential conversation with Johnson about China and Czechoslovakia.
  - Johnson, Walter C., 1956-1961 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Johnson, William Houston, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Johnston, Eric A., 1962 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Johnston, Richard J. H., 1944-1959 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Jones, Arthur W.
  - Jones, Enid, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Jones, Evan J., 1935, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Jones, George, 1936, 1951-1953 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Jones, Howard P., 1954-1966 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Jones, Jesse H., 1934-1954 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Jones, Richard L., Jr., 1943, 1956-1957, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Jones, W. Alton, 1945-1956 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, Lewis E., 1953-1961 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Jordan, Michael J., 1962 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Jordan, William K., 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Jorden, William J., 1954-1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Joseph, David H., 1948-1961, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Joyce, Robert P. and Jane Joyce, 1948-1949 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar, 1930-1931, 1947-1957 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Kaempffert was the NYT's science writer and a member of the Editorial Board. The papers in this folder deal with his return to the NYT in 1931 and the issue of writing for other publications, his winning of a special Lasker citation in 1954, and his death in 1956.
  - Kagan, Leo B.
    See entry A
  - Kahn, Ely Jacques and Beatrice Kahn, 1939-1967 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Mrs. Kahn was the widow of Leo Sulzberger, AHS's older brother, and the mother of Cyrus L. Sulzberger. She married Ely Kahn in 1938, and died in 1962. Kahn remarried in 1964.Mrs. Kahn was the widow of Leo Sulzberger, AHS's older brother, and the mother of Cyrus L. Sulzberger. She married Ely Kahn in 1938, and died in 1962. Kahn remarried in 1964.
  - Kaiser, Henry J., 1958-1961 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Kalb, Bernard, 1957-1968 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Kamp, Joseph P., 1943 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Kandel, Myron, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Kant, S., 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Kanter, Donald, 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Karr, David, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Karsh, Yousuf, 1951-1962 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Kasai, Juiji G., 1950 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Kase, Toshikazu
  - Kassern, Tadeusz, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Kastor, Alfred B., 1952, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Kastor, Robert N., 1961-1963 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Katzander, Howard L. and Barbara Adler Katzander, 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Kauffman, Samuel H., 1953-1965 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Kauffman, Stanley
  - Kaufman, Enit, 1941-1943 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Kaufman, George S., 1962 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Kaufman, Irving R., 1953-1956 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Keating, Geoffrey J., 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Kefauver, Estes, 1955-1960 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Keller, Christine Hegi, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Keller, Helen, 1949-1955 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Keller, K. T., 1942, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Kellner, Joseph, 1961-1968 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Kellner, Paul, 1941, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Kellogg, Frank B.
  - Kelly, Mary, 1954-1966 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Kelly, Raymond J., 1952-1967 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Kempner, S. Marshall, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Kemsley, Viscount (Gomer Berry), 1938-1968 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Kennan, George F., 1951-1964 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1962 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Kennedy, John F. and Jacqueline Bouvier Kennedy, 1956-1963 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Includes correspondence about luncheon invitations, White House dinners, personal matters, and Anthony Lewis' memorandum reviewing Kennedy's attitude on Joseph McCarthy (1960).
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., 1940, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Includes Arthur Krock's private memorandum on his conversation with Kennedy in 1940, in which Kennedy explained his resignation as ambassador to Great Britain and surrounding circumstances.
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1960-1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy, Stephen P., 1956 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Kenney, George C., 1959-1960 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Kent, Annette J., 1953-1959 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Kent, Frank R., 1958 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1928-1934, 1940, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Kerensky, Alexander, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Kerr, Walter, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Keys, Ancel
  - Kiep, Hanna, 1947-1952, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Mrs. Kiep was the widow of the German Consul General in New York who was executed by the Nazis in 1934. They had been friends of the Sulzbergers. This folder contains correspondence kealing with AHS's efforts to help Mrs. Kiep and her two daughters (197-1952); Mrs. Kiep's correspondence with Mrs. Sulzberger (1964); and papers about a memorial to Otto Kiep (1965).Mrs. Kiep was the widow of the German Consul General in New York who was executed by the Nazis in 1934. They had been friends of the Sulzbergers. This folder contains correspondence kealing with AHS's efforts to help Mrs. Kiep and her two daughters (197-1952); Mrs. Kiep's correspondence with Mrs. Sulzberger (1964); and papers about a memorial to Otto Kiep (1965).
  - Kieran, John, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Kihss, Peter
  - Kilpatrick, John Reed, 1949, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Kimberly, James C.
  - Kimberly, John R., 1951-1956 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - King, Ernest J., 1945 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - King, Walter R., 1946-1948, 1954-1959 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Kingsford-Smith, Charles
  - Kingsley, Elizabeth
  - Kingsley, J. Donald, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1953 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Kinsolving, Arthur Lee, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Kintner, Robert E., 1944 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Kipling, Rudyard, 1936-1937 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Kirchwey, Freda
  - Kirk, Alan G., 1952 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Kirk, Grayson, 1955-1968 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Kirk, H. David, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Kirstein, George
  - Kishi, Nobusuke
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1959-1961 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Klauber, Edward, 1940-1945 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Kleberg, Robert J., Jr., 1953-1959 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Klein, Harris J., 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Kleitz, William L.
  - Kline, Charles, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Kline, Nathan, 1959-1960 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Kluckhohn, Frank L., 1930-1951 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Knapp, Elizabeth Mercer, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Knauth, Oswald, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Knecht, Marcel, 1955, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Knight, Goodwin J., 1955 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Knight, John S., 1947-1968 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Knight, Ruth M., 1953-1958 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Knollys, Viscount, 1949-1966 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. and Blanche Knopf, 1939-1968 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
    Includes papers concerning the Knopf publishing house could not be segregated from those dealing with Mr. and Mrs. Knopf.
  - Knowland, Joseph R., 1954-1961 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Knowland, William F., 1955 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Knowles, Charles J.
  - Knox, Frank
    - General, 1936-1944 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, 1952-1960 (Box 292, Folder 1-3)
  - Knox, William E., 1952-1968 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
  - Knulst, Cornelius and Anne Raick Knulst
  - Koenig, Wirth H., 1965-1967 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1944-1956 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Kohler, Max J., 1934 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Kohler, Walter J., Jr., 1956 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Kolb, Richard, 1955-1964 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Kops, Waldemar, 1941-1945 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Kornitzer, Bela, 1948-1960 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Kory, Irma, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Koshland, Daniel E. and Lucile Koshlan, 1959-1968 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Kotelawela, John
  - Kouzminsky, Michael
  - Krafft, Charles J.
  - Kramer, A. Walter, 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Kreutzer, S. Stanley, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Kridel, William J., 1940, 1956, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Kriendler, I. Robert, 1945-1968 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Krinovitz, Irving, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Krock, Arthur and Martha Krock
    These folders contain AHS's correspondence with and about Krock, mostly in connection with Krock's career and personal matters, Krock's column, "In the Nation," and readers' comments on diverse columns.
    - 1940-1968 (Box 39, Folder 1-8)
    - 1927-1939 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Krout, John A., 1961-1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Krueger, Walter, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Krumb, Henry, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Krumm, John M., 1961, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1959-1960 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Kubitschek, Juscelino
  - Kuhn, Ferdinand, Jr., 1930-1939, 1946, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Kuhn, Fritz
  - Kuhn, Irene Corbally
  - Kupferman, Murray, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Labalme, George and Annette Labalme, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Labouisse, Henry R., 1954-1961 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Lachenbruch, Mabel Hays, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Lacy, William S. B., 1955, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Ladue, Ralph E., 1942 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Laemmle, Carl, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello H., 1934-1957 (Box 40, Folder 17-22)
    These folders contain letters, memoranda, and clippings documenting LaGuardia's often stormy relations with the NYT and other newspapers. The principal issues were his activities connected with World War II and the postwar food shortages, his use of his radio program to disseminate his releases in preference to regular dealings with the press, and diverse problems of New York City.
  - Lake, Simon
  - Lambton, Anne, 1954-1967 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1951, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Lamont, Thomas S., 1955-1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1935, 1941, 1948-1957 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Landman, Isaac, 1938-1944 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Landon, Alfred M., 1936-1942, 1950, 1957-1961 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1947-1948, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Lane, Calli, 1956-1966 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Lane, Charles C., 1942-1968 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Lane, Chester C.
  - Lane, Frederick E., 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Lane, Robert P., 1946 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Lane, Winthrop D.
  - Lang, Lillian Keller, 1935, 1954-1960 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Lang, Joseph, 1952-1954 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Langlie, Arthur B., 1957 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Lanham, Charles T., 1948-1967 (Box 41, Folder 15-16)
  - Lansing, Robert
  - Lapham, Roger D., 1949 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Larmon, Sigurd S., 1956-1962 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Larsen, Henry L., 1946 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Larsen, Roy E., 1954 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Larssen, Lennie, 1955-1958 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Lasker, Albert D.
  - Lasker, Mary, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Lauck, Gerold, 1941, 1952-1954 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Laurence, William L.
    Includes Leslie Groves' letters to AHS praising Laurence's role in covering the story of the atomic bomb (1945), memoranda by Laurence, Edwin L. James, and AHS about Laurence's desire to be a science writer at large, letters and other documents about Laurence's role in the discovery of a plant yielding a cortisone-like substance for the treatment of arthritis and other diseases (1949), and a memorandum on Laurence's appointment as science editor (1956).
    - 1951-1968 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - 1943-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Lawrence, David, 1942, 1961, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Lawrence, Gertrude, 1946-1948 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Lawrence, Justus B., 1955-1962 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Lawrence, William H., 1945-1961 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Layton, Walter, 1949-1951, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Lazar, Albert, 1954, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Lazareff, Pierre Helene Lazareff, 1948, 1955, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Lazaron, Morris S., 1935-1968 (Box 42, Folder 9-12)
  - Le Boutillier, Philip, 1949, 1953-1955 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Lee, Kenneth, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Lees, Bob, 1954-1956, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Lehman, Florence Levi, 1955-1956, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Lehman, Herbert H. and Edith Lehman, 1928-1963 (Box 42, Folder 17-18)
  - Lehman, Orin, 1958-1966 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Lehrbas, Lloyd, 1945-1948 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Leidesdorf, Samuel D.
  - Leisure, George S., 1954-1967 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Leland, Waldo G., 1956 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Lemanchec, Yvonne, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Lemnitzer, Lyman L., 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Leopold, Nathan F., 1957 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Lequerica, Jose Felix
  - Leroux, Germaine and Milos Safranek, 1938-1944, 1950-1958 (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
  - Leslie, Jane Scales, 1950-1967 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Leviero, Anthony, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Levin, Meyer, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Levitt, Arthur, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Levy, Frederick, Sr. and Frederick Levy, Jr., 1955-1956, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Levy, Joseph M. and Edith Levy, 1930-1948, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 9-10)
  - Levy, Robert L., 1949-1967 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Lewin, Isaac
  - Lewis, Anthony, 1956-1966 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Lewis, Chester M., 1955-1965 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, Flora
  - Lewis, John L., 1937 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Lewisohn, Ludwig
  - Ley, Willy, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Leysmith, Walter F., 1939-1953 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Li, K. C., 1961 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Lichteim, George
  - Lie, Trygve
  - Lieberman, Henry R., 1946-1957 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Liebes, Martin, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Liebling, A.J.
  - Liebmann, Philip, 1952-1958 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Liechtenstein, Ferdinand, 1933-1935 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Lifschultz, Emanuel L.
  - Liggett, Walter, 1935 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Lilienthal, David E., 1939-1967 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Lincoln, Edmond E., 1936, 1941, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Lincoln, Leroy A., 1955-1957 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Lindbergh, Charles A. and Anne Lindbergh
    - General, 1933-1941, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Includes memoranda, clippings, and other documents about Lauren D. Lyman's scoop on Lindbergh's departure for England and copyright infringement by Hearst papers (1935-1937), about Lindbergh's attitude towards Germany and World War II, and Russell Owen's report on interview with Lindbergh (1941).
    - Autographed portrait of Charles A. Lindbergh, 1928 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Lindsay, John V., 1960-1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Linen, James A., 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Linkletter, Art, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Lippman, Walter
  - Lissner, Will
  - Listowel, Judith, 1953-1954 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. and Mary Litchfield, 1957-1959 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Little, Clarence Cook
  - Littledale, Harold A., 1941-1945, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Littlefield, Walter, 1936-1944, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Livingston, James D., Jr., 1953 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Lleras Camargo, Alberto
  - Lloyd, Selwyn, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Lloyd George, David, 1935, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Locke, Edwin A., Jr., 1945-1951 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1960-1965 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Lodge, John Davis, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Loeb, Louis M., 1941-1968 (Box 44, Folder 15-16)
  - Loeb, Robert F., 1959-1961 (Box 44, Folder 17)